Your Hub for Home Services

    Track all alerts and offers  
    through the Neighborly app[Open app store __](https://www.neighborly.com/about/the-neighborly-app) 

* [1 (855) 217-8437](tel:1 (855) 217-8437) Call Us 24/7

* About

* Expert Tips

### Need a hand around the house?

Enter ZIP Code 

Find local help >

[__1 (855) 217-8437](tel:1 (855) 217-8437) Call Us 24/7 Schedule Now

© 2024 Neighborly Company and its affiliates. All rights reserved. Neighborly is a registered trademark of Neighborly Assetco LLC. Each location is independently owned and operated. State, provincial, and local laws may impact the services this independently owned and operated franchise location may perform at this time. Please contact the franchise location for additional information.

Privacy Policy
==============

Online Privacy Policy
---------------------

Thank you for visiting this website (this “Site”), which is owned and operated by Neighborly (“Neighborly,” “we,” “us,” and “our”).

Effective Date
--------------

January 1, 2023

Table of Contents
-----------------

Scope of This Policy
--------------------

This online privacy policy (this “Policy”) applies only to information collected through Neighborly-Owned websites on which it is posted. It does not apply to third-party platforms, such as websites owned by our franchisees, social media websites, vendor pages, websites of other corporations, limited liability companies, etc. or to Neighborly-owned websites or other Neighborly owned platforms on which it is not posted. It also does not apply to information collected through other channels, such as over the phone or in person.

By installing any third-party application, you are authorizing such third-party application to perform the actions and/or share with the third-party application the information communicated to Neighborly, or requested from Neighborly to perform the actions and/or share with the third-party application the information communicated to Neighborly, or requested from Neighborly. Neighborly is going to send that information through the third-party application, which will then go through the internet. Neighborly shall not be held responsible for any dissemination, use, misuse, and/or disclosure of the user's information through use of this or any third-party application.

Some of the information we collect through this Site may be “personal information”—information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us. Other information may be non-personally identifiable, such as information collected by cookies.

This Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by additional privacy notices (“Privacy Notices”), provided at the time we collect your information. For example, certain pages of this Site may contain Privacy Notices providing more details about the information we collect on those particular pages, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the ways we use that information. In other cases, specific Privacy Notices may be required to comply with the privacy laws of one of the countries, provinces, or states in which we do business.

Your Consent
------------

By using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure, and transfer of your information as described in this Policy (and any Privacy Notices that apply to you). If you do not consent to the collection, use, disclosure, and transfer of your information as described in this Policy (and any Privacy Notices that apply to you), you may not use this Site. If you have questions about this Policy, or any Privacy Notice, please contact us using the information provided [in the section below](#Questions).

Our Terms of Use
----------------

This Policy is part of the [Terms of Use](https://www.neighborly.com/terms-of-use) that govern your use of this Site. A link to our [Terms of Use](https://www.neighborly.com/terms-of-use) is provided at the bottom of each page of this Site.

Your Choices
------------

_In General._ We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use, and disclose your information. This Policy describes some of your choices, such as your choice to opt out of receiving “[cookies](#Cookies).” We may ask you to indicate your choices at the time and on the page where you provide your information.

_Do Not Track Mechanisms_. California law requires this Policy to address how we respond to any “Do-Not-Track (‘DNT’) signal” delivered by your browser. Because of the changing state of technology and indecision within the industry regarding the meaning of DNT signals, we currently do not make any guarantee that we will honor DNT signals.

_Previously Expressed Preferences._ You may change previously expressed preferences regarding how we use your information. If at any time you wish to be taken off our mailing lists, please contact us using the information provided [contact section below](#Questions).

This Policy May Change
----------------------

Neighborly reserves the right to update or modify this Policy and any Privacy Notice, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of the Policy or Privacy Notice on this Site. These changes will only apply to the information we collect after we have posted the revised Policy or Privacy Notice on this Site.

Your use of this Site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all information collected from or about you after the revised Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Policy. You may access the current version of this Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked “Privacy” at the bottom of each page of the public areas of this Site.

Information We Collect
----------------------

_Information You Manually Provide_. Neighborly collects the information you manually provide (using your keyboard, mouse, or touchpad) when you use this Site, for example, we collect the information you provide when you request service, express interest in becoming a franchisee, send us questions, or otherwise interact with this Site. Some of the information you manually provide may be personal information, such as your name and contact information.

_Information from Third-Party Social Media Platforms._ You may be able to register with, log on to, or enhance your profile on this Site by choosing to automatically populate the requested data fields with information you previously provided to a third-party social media platform (such as Facebook or Twitter). By doing this, you are asking the third-party platform to send us information, including personal information, from your profile on that platform. We treat that information as we do any other information you give to us when you register, log on, or enhance your profile.

_Information from Your Browser or Device._ Neighborly collects information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser or mobile device. This information typically includes your IP address, the name of your operating system, the name and version of your browser, the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit.

The information we receive may depend on your browser or device settings. The information we receive from your web browser and device typically is not, in and of itself, personally identifiable. However, we may combine it with other information in an attempt to identify you or we may combine it with information that does identify you.

_Information Collected by Cookies and Other Technologies_. We use “cookies” and other technologies to collect information and support certain features of this Site. For example, we may use these technologies to:

* collect information about the ways visitors use this Site—which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page.
* support the features and functionality of this Site—for example, to save you the trouble of reentering information already in our database or to prompt the settings you established on previous visits.
* personalize your experience when you use this Site, and
* improve our marketing efforts, including through use of targeted advertising.

The information we collect using cookies and similar technologies is not, in and of itself, personally identifiable, but we may link it to personal information that you provide. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit this Site, you may be unable to use all the functionality of this Site if your browser rejects our cookies.

Information About Third-Party Cookies
-------------------------------------

In addition to the cookies, Neighborly delivers to your computer or mobile device through this Site, certain third parties may deliver cookies to you for a variety of reasons. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with our Sites. To learn more about Google Analytics, [read the Google Analytics definition here.](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer or mobile device for the purpose of tracking your online behaviors over time and across nonaffiliated websites and/or delivering targeted advertisements either on this Site or on other websites.

You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on our Sites. For example, if you don’t want information about your visit to this Site sent to Google Analytics, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by [selecting a browser add-on here.](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) Please note that the Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to Neighborly.

In addition, if you would like to opt-out of having interest-based information collected by certain entities during your visits to this Site or other websites, please [select collection opt-out here.](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) You will be directed to an industry-developed website that contains mechanisms for choosing whether each listed entity may collect and use data for online behavioral advertising purposes.

It may be that some of the third parties that collect interest-based information on this Site do not participate in the industry-developed opt-out website, in which case the best way to avoid third-party tracking of your online behaviors may be through your browser settings and deletion of cookies. Please note that the industry-developed opt-out mechanism is device and browser specific. If you wish to opt-out from having interest-based information collected by participating entities across all devices and browsers, you need take the steps outlined above from each device and browser.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

Generally, we use the information we collect through this Site:

* to provide the information, products, and services you request.
* to provide you with effective customer service.
* to provide you with a personalized experience when you use this Site.
* to contact you with information and notices related to your use of this Site.
* to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us).
* to invite you to participate in surveys and provide Feedback to us (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us).
* to improve the content, functionality, and usability of this Site.
* to better understand your needs and interests.
* to improve our products and services.
* to improve our marketing and promotional efforts.
* for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes, and
* for any other purpose identified in an applicable Privacy Notice, click-through agreement, or other agreement between you and us.

We transfer customer information to franchisees, service providers, vendors and other companies who globally support our business, such as providing services requested through this website, technical infrastructure services, analyzing how our services are used, measuring the effectiveness of ads and services, providing customer service, facilitating payments, or conducting surveys. These companies must adhere to strict confidentiality obligations in a way that is consistent with this privacy policy and the agreements we enter into with them.

How We Share Your Information
-----------------------------

_With Third-Party Vendors_. Neighborly shares information collected through this Site with third-party vendors who act for us or on our behalf. For example, we may use third-party vendors to design and operate this Site; to conduct surveys; and to help us with our promotional efforts. These third-party vendors may need information about you to perform their functions.

_With Other Users of this Site_. You may be able to submit User-Generated Content on or through this Site. In this Policy, “User-Generated Content” or “UGC” refers to content that you post using the social networking tools we make available to you and that does not constitute “Feedback” (as that term is defined in our [Terms of Use](https://www.neighborly.com/terms-of-use). Any personal information contained in UGC can be read, collected, or used by others.

In addition, we may use UGC you submit for advertising campaigns and other promotions. We may or may not use your name in connection with such use, and we may or may not seek your consent before using the content for such purposes. Therefore, you should have no expectation of privacy with respect to UGC you submit on or through this Site.

_With Third-Party Social Media Platforms._ We may provide functionality on this Site that allows you to automatically post information about the actions you take on this Site to a third-party social media platform (such as Facebook or Twitter). If you choose to take advantage of this functionality, people with access to your profile on the third-party platform may be able to see the actions you have taken—for example, the products or services you have purchased. Thus, you should have no expectation of privacy in those actions.

Further, if you choose to link your profile on this Site with an account on a third-party social media platform, we may share the information in your profile with that third-party platform. We may also use third-party social media platforms to offer you interest-based ads. To offer such ads, we may convert your email address into a unique value which can be matched by our partner company with a user on their platform. Although we do not provide any personal information to these platform vendors, they may gain insights about individuals who respond to the ads we serve.

_Within Neighborly Corporate Family._ We may share information collected through this Site with other companies in Neighborly corporate structure. These affiliate companies are permitted to use your information for their own marketing purposes and in a manner otherwise consistent with this Policy.

_With our Franchisees_. We may share information collected through this Site with our franchisees, which may be permitted to use your information for their own marketing purposes and in any manner otherwise consistent with this Policy.

_With Other, Carefully Selected Business Partners_. From time to time, we may share your information with selected third parties for their own marketing purposes. For example, we may partner with third parties to sponsor contests or other promotions, and we may share with these third parties the information you submit to us to participate in the contest or take advantage of the promotion. Before doing so, however, we may offer you the opportunity to “opt out” or “opt in,” as required by applicable law. We do not share your SMS opt-in data and consent with external third parties for their own marketing purposes.

_In Aggregate or De-Identified Form._ We use information collected through this Site to create a compiled, aggregate view of usage patterns. We may share aggregate information with third parties so they can better understand our user base. We may also share, with third parties, information about how particular individuals use this Site, but only on a de-identified basis (“Individualized Data”). Individualized Data is not personally identifiable, but it does reflect the usage patterns of a particular Site user, as opposed to Site users collectively.

_As Part of a Business Transfer_. Your information may be transferred to successor organization if, for example, we transfer the ownership or operation of this Site to another organization or if we merge with another organization or liquidate our assets. If such a transfer occurs, the successor organization’s use of your information will still be subject to this Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.

_To Comply with Laws and Protect Our Rights and the Rights of Others_. We may disclose your information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose your information to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to protect the security of this Site; to enforce or apply our online [Terms of Use](https://www.neighborly.com/terms-of-use) or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.

_As Described in a Privacy Notice or Click-Through Agreement._ We reserve the right to disclose your information as described in any Privacy Notice posted on a page of this Site where you provide that information. By providing your information on that page you will be consenting to the disclosure of your information as described in that privacy notice. We also reserve the right to disclose your information as described in any click–through agreement to which you have agreed.

How We Protect Your Information
-------------------------------

Neighborly takes reasonable precautions to provide a level of security appropriate to the sensitivity of the information we collect. Although we use reasonable measures to help protect your information against unauthorized use or disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet or stored in our databases and will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

You must be at least 13 years old to have our permission to use this Site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 13 years of age. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use this Site.

Links to Other Websites
-----------------------

This Policy applies only to Neighborly-owned websites on which it is posted. Neighborly and its affiliates operate many different websites for different purposes and in different countries, where different laws may apply. If you visit another Neighborly website, please take a moment to review the privacy policy posted on that site to learn what information may be collected through that site and how it is processed.

This Site may also contain links to websites that are not operated by Neighborly or its affiliates. These links are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the products sold or information provided through these websites, nor any association with their operators. Neighborly does not control these websites and is not responsible for their data practices.

Any information you provide to third parties on their websites is covered under their privacy and data collection policies and is not covered by this Policy. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information.

Access to Your Information
--------------------------

If you would like to review, correct, and update the personal information you have provided to us through this Site, please contact us using the information provided [in the section below](#Questions). We will respond to your request within a reasonable time or within the time limit set out by applicable privacy law. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request, as required by applicable law.

Retention of Personal Information
---------------------------------

Neighborly retains the personal information collected on this Site as long as necessary to provide the services, products and information you request or as permitted by applicable law.

Site Servers May Be Located Outside Your Home Country.
------------------------------------------------------

Neighborly is a U.S. corporation and this Site is intended for a U.S. audience. The servers that support this Site and on which we store the information you provide to us through this Site may be located in a country other than where you reside. U.S. data protection laws may not provide as much protection as the data protection laws in force in some other countries.

However, we will process your information in accordance with this Policy no matter where our data is stored. If you are located in a country other than the United States, by using this Site you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States.

Governing Law
-------------

This Policy shall be governed under the laws of the State of Texas, United States of America without regard to its conflicts of law provisions.

Questions About This Policy or Neighborly's Data Practices
----------------------------------------------------------

If you have questions or concerns about this Policy, any Privacy Notice, or Neighborly’s data practices, please contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.neighborly.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) You may also contact us at: 800.490.7501

**Should you no longer wish to receive our email, please click on the unsubscribe link supplied in each message received and/or contact us via telephone at 800.490.7501 or via mail Attn: Privacy Policy, Neighborly 1020 N. University Parks Dr., Waco, TX 76707.**

[1 (855) 217-8437Call Us on 1 (855) 217-8437](tel: 1 (855) 217-8437)Call Us 24/7

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 

© 2024 Neighborly Company and its affiliates. All rights reserved. Neighborly is a registered trademark of Neighborly Assetco LLC. Each location is independently owned and operated. State, provincial, and local laws may impact the services this independently owned and operated franchise location may perform at this time. Please contact the franchise location for additional information.

[Chat with us](https://www.livechatinc.com/chat-with/11799645/), powered by [LiveChat](https://www.livechatinc.com/?welcome "LiveChat - opens in new tab")

© 2024 Neighborly Company and its affiliates. All Rights Reserved.

The Done Right Promise:
-----------------------

**We stand by the promise to do the job right.**

Our independently owned franchise owners will perform services in a professional, workmanlike manner, consistent with industry standards.

Terms, conditions, and exclusions apply. Services performed by independently owned and operated franchises.

The Done Right Promise:
-----------------------

**Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetuer diam.**

Neighborly consectetuer diam nonumy. Lorem ipsum lelelit dolor sit amet consectetuer diam nonumy sed lelelit orem ipsum.

Call us directly at [Call phone number(888) 861-4344](tel:(888) 861-4344)

×

Tell us where you’re located.
-----------------------------

ZIP/Postal Code

We need a little more information.
----------------------------------

\* indicates a required field

Address \* 

Apartment, suite, unit, etc. (optional) 

City \* 

State \* Select a state

ZIP/Postal code \* 

Back Next

We’re sorry. We don’t currently provide service to .
----------------------------------------------------

How can we help you?
--------------------

Service type: \*

 Residential

 Commercial

 Emergency

 Auto

Type the service you’re looking for here:

* * *

or choose from the popular services for  [change](#):

Select a specific service below to proceed.
-------------------------------------------

Local services available in and

We’ve got you covered!
----------------------

Your local professional in **:**

Warranty Information
--------------------

\* indicates a required field

Service \*

What is brand of the appliance\* \- select one

Appliance Problems:

 Failure to start

 My appliance is covered by a manufacturer’s warranty or service contract.

Back Next

How often can we help?
----------------------

\* indicates a required field

Frequency of Cleaning: \*

 Recurring

 One-time

Frequency?

 Weekly

 Every other week

 Once every 4 weeks

Is this a move-in/move-out clean? \*

 Yes

 No

Back Next

Schedule Date and Time
----------------------

For EMERGENCY scheduling please call (888) 861-4344 otherwise choose from our scheduling options below.

Previous

Next

Date and Time Selected:

Back Next

About Your Home
---------------

\* indicates a required field

Square Feet \* 

Bedrooms \* Select an option 1 2 3 4 5

Bathrooms \* Select an option 1 2 3 4 5

Where did you hear about us? \* \-Select one

Back Next

Estimate
--------

### Our full house cleaning includes everything on this list and more:

* Dust baseboards, light fixtures, furniture, sills
* Vacuum/Mop all floors, carpets, and stairs
* Clean showers, tubs, toilets, and sinks
* Clean mirrors, glass, counters and tile
* Dust all furniture and furnishings

### One Time Cleaning Estimate, based upon information provided:

Please call us for an estimate:

Note: Recurring cleans are a lower flat rate fee. One-Time Clean: All pricing is based on a two-person, fully-insured cleaning team.

### Add On Services

Customized cleans are available to meet your specific needs; however, additional charges may apply.

* Refrigerator cleaning
* Oven cleaning
* Clean inside cabinets/drawers

### Our full house cleaning includes everything on this list and more:

* Dust baseboards, light fixtures, furniture, sills
* Vacuum/mop all floors, carpets, and stairs
* Clean showers, tubs, toilets, and sinks
* Clean mirrors, glass, counters and tile
* Dust all furniture and furnishings

Back Next

To submit your request faster, [sign in](#) to your account

Contact Information
-------------------

\* indicates a required field

First Name \* 

Last Name \* 

Email \* 

Phone Number \* 

 Mobile

By entering your email address, you agree to receive emails about services, updates or promotions, and you agree to the [Terms](https://www.neighborly.com/terms-of-use) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.neighborly.com/privacy-policy). You may unsubscribe at any time.

Back Next

Service Address
---------------

\* indicates a required field

Address \* 

Apartment, suite, unit, etc. (optional) 

City \* 

State \* Select a state

ZIP/Postal code \* 

Back NextSubmit

About Your Service Needs
------------------------

What services are you interested in?

 Auto

 Residential

 Commercial

 Need Improvement

 General Enquiry

Back Next

Vehicle Information
-------------------

\* indicates a required field

Year \* 

Body Style \* 

Make \* 

VIN 

Model \* 

License plate 

Back Next

Neighborly is a family of home service brands that share a commitment to providing you with an outstanding level of service.

 Windshield Repair (Damage is smaller than a quarter and not in your field of vision)

 Headlight Restoration

Need to replace

 Driver Side Front Door

 Passenger Side Front Door

 Driver Side Back Door

 Passenger Side Back Door

 Driver Side Vent Glass

 Passenger Side Vent Glass

 Driver Side Quarter Glass

 Passenger Side Quarter Glass

 Back Glass

 Something Else

Back Skip

Type of Service

 Drop-off at Shop near you

 Have us come to you with Mobile service

Street Address 

ZIP Code 

Form of payment

 Personal (Cash, Check or Charge)

 Insurance Claim

Insurance Company 

Deductible Amount 

Policy Number 

How did you hear about us? \* Select one

Back Skip

Service Details
---------------

\* indicates a required field

What space needs to be painted?\* Select Interior Exterior Please select an item

Please describe your service needs:

What floor is the appliance located? Select Basement 1st Floor 2nd Floor 3rd Floor 4th Floor or Higher

Show us the issue. Attach up to 3 images:

xxxxxxxx.jpg[Remove](#)

Attach image.

Where did you hear about us? \* Where did you hear about us?

**Diagnostic Fee** - Our in-home service professionals will look at your appliance, diagnose the problem, and give you an exact quote. If you choose not to have the repair done, you pay only the $ diagnostic fee.

**Inspection Fee:** An inspection fee of $ will be charged for this appointment.

Back Submit

Alert
-----

Your updated address is serviced by another location. Please re-select your preferred date and time and proceed to the next steps to verify your information for the new location.

Alert
-----

Based on your updated address, your request will be sent to the appropriate service location.

Alert
-----

Your updated address is serviced by a new location. However, the new location does not currently offer a scheduling option. Someone will contact you to setup your appointment date and time.

Alert
-----

Your updated address is serviced by another location. The new location offers a scheduling option.

Please select your preferred date and time and verify your information for your appointment.

Call us directly at

User Profile
------------

* * *

### Personal Information

### Name

### Email

Primary

### Password [Change](#)

### Phone[](#)

### Address[](#)

### Preferred Method of Contact

*  Phone
    
*  Text (standard text and data rates apply)
    
*  Email

Call us directly at

Edit Name
---------

* * *

First Name 

Last Name 

Apply Changes

Call us directly at

Edit Phone Number
-----------------

* * *

Delete

Phone This is number already exist

 Primary Phone

 SMS/Text

 Voice call

Would you like to receive the latest updates, offers, and helpful tips?

 Yes, sign me up!

By signing up, I agree to Neighborly’s Terms of Use and [Terms and Conditions](#). I also acknowledge \[Neighborly\]’s [Privacy Statement](#).

Apply Changes

Call us directly at

User Profile
------------

* * *

### Verify OTP

Verify

Call us directly at

Edit Address
------------

* * *

Delete

Address 

Address 2 

City 

State State

ZIP Code 

Type Residential Business

 Primary Address

Apply Changes

-------------------------------------------------------------------

**Phone Verification**

To protect your account we need to verify your phone number

 Mobile Work Home

**Get verification code by:**

 SMS/Text

 Voice call

Continue

-------------------------------------------------------------------

### Verify OTP

Enter your 6 digit verfication code

Verify Cancel

-------------------------------------------------------------------

Welcome to Neighborly
---------------------

Your account was created successfully.

Home

**New credentials required:**

Unlinking this account will require you to create a username and password to access the web application

Cancel Continue

Account login Successfully updated

ok

Error
-----

Continue
